{
    "id": "e6bbf5d8cffc4a7e99eba81bcc8ed512",
    "title": "Prepositions Of Time",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will call you …………………….. Friday.",
            "description": "We use on with days.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "295ad0a8a501472c926438d0036a0093"
        },
        {
            "question": "They got married ………………………… the week after Christmas.",
            "description": "We use in with longer periods like weeks.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c93afd524e034980b0da84ec6e2bfd3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are having a party ………………………… Easter Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9422763e2143424da30066ab471d30ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "My birthday is ……………………….. May 18th.",
            "description": "We use on before dates.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c1abfc523034a42a5d76bb5d0e189a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Chennai is hot …………………………. summer.",
            "description": "We use in with seasons. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9a0b13cfa60a4b6aa4409aa776f16dea"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing …………………………… the weekend?",
            "description": "On the weekend is more common in American English and at the weekend is common in British English.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7ffabc065764f6895944a9bb778567f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am visiting my parents ………………………….. Christmas day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "35f078074e6343eea80ee95e3be5a1f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The palace was built …………………………….. the 16th century.",
            "description": "We use in with longer periods like centuries. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "debb0fe0d2944f05a688d77dafa5c627"
        },
        {
            "question": "I work best …………………………… the evening.",
            "description": "We use in with evening, morning and afternoon.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "73efa5013b4149079a607f8e0e94444d"
        },
        {
            "question": "See you …………………………… Sunday morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ad05d871b8e4e37ae392dfe26a3bfd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ……………………………. a cold evening in January.",
            "description": "We use on before evening when we say which evening we are talking about.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81b3d4a9dcc4406baa0873d7e0908d66"
        },
        {
            "question": "They finished the job …………………………… a week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e797532291fc44aab52b791e6b0c2449"
        }
    ]
}